iuj.ac.jp 2014-11-22

# IUJ: Privacy Statement

IUJ Top > Privacy Statement

**Privacy Statement**

Protecting your privacy is important to IUJ. We hope the following policy will help you understand how IUJ collects, uses, and safeguards the personal information you provide on our website.

**Information Collection**  
If you browse IUJ website, you do so anonymously. We don't collect personal information including your email address. We do log your IP address (the Internet address of your computer) to give us an idea of which parts of our website you visit and how long you spend there. But we do not link your IP address to anything personally identifiable. The only other information automatically provided to us is the type of computer and operating system you are using. Your browser supplies us with this information. Like many other commercial websites, the IUJ website may use a standard technology called a "cookie" to collect information about how you use the site.

At times we may request that you voluntarily supply us with personal information, such as your email address and postal address, for purposes such as corresponding with us, registering at a site, requesing information, or participating in an online survey. When you request admissions forms from IUJ, for example, we collect your name, nationality, address, email address, and other information that is important for our admissions process.

**Information Use**  
If you provide us with your email or postal address, or have done so in the past, we will ask you if we can use it to send you updates on the latest IUJ announcements. We also ask if you want us to include you on any email list before sending email to you. If you do not want us to contact you, you can choose to "opt out," at any time and IUJ will respect your wishes. 

We may use information that you have given us to learn more about our visitors so that we can enhance our online information. We may also use the information to inform you about new programs or services that may be of interest to you. These offers may be based on information you provided in your initial transaction with us or in surveys. We do not share your profile with anyone else outside of IUJ without your consent, and no one else can access your information.

**Declining Email**  
IUJ provides you with an easy means to decline to receive email. At any time, you may request to discontinue receiving these offers from us by simply replying to the email and informing us of your preferences. All email offers that you receive from IUJ will tell you how to decline further email offers.

**Data Security**  
IUJ is fully committed to data security. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information you provide to us online. However, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure the security of the information you transmit to us. In this regard, we urge you to take every precaution to protect your personal data while you are on the Internet. At a minimum, we encourage you to change your passwords often, using a combination of letters and numbers, and make sure that you are using a secure browser as you use the Internet.

IUJ privacy policy is subject to change at any time and without notice. For updates, please check this page on a regular basis.
